// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which planet is known as Red Planet ?",
        answer: "Mars",
        options: [
            "Venus",
            "Mars",
            "Jupiter",
            "Saturn"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which planet is the closest to the Sun??",
        answer: "Mercury",
        options: [
            "Mercury",
            "Venus",
            "Mars",
            "Earth"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which planet is the largest in our solar system?",
        answer: "Jupiter",
        options: [
            "Earth",
            "Neptune",
            "Jupiter",
            "Uranus"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which planet is known for its beautiful ring system?",
        answer: "Saturn",
        options: [
            "Saturn",
            "Uranus",
            "Jupiter",
            "Neptune"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which planet is often called the Evening Star or Morning Star?",
        answer: "Venus",
        options: [
            "Venus",
            "Mars",
            "Mercury",
            "Jupiter"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which planet has the most significant tilt in its rotational axis, giving it extreme seasons?",
        answer: "Uranus",
        options: [
            "Uranus",
            "Mars",
            "Saturn",
            "Jupiter"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which planet is known for its stunning blue color due to methane in its atmosphere?",
        answer: "Neptune",
        options: [
            "Uranus",
            "Jupiter",
            "Neptune",
            "Saturn"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which planet has the Great Red Spot, a giant storm system?",
        answer: "Jupiter",
        options: [
            "Jupiter",
            "Saturn",
            "Mars",
            "Earth"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which planet is known as the Ice Giant ?",
        answer: "Neptune",
        options: [
            "Uranus",
            "Neptune",
            "Saturn",
            "Jupiter"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which planet is often referred to as the Twin of Earth due to its similarities in size and density?",
        answer: "Venus",
        options: [
            "Venus",
            "Mars",
            "Mercury",
            "Uranus"
        ]
    }
];

//# sourceMappingURL=index.3ac99f0c.js.map
